NAA History Committee Oral History Interview Masters 6004 OHM
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NAA History Committee Oral History Interview Masters
1990-2006
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Academy of Arbitrators (NAA)
6004 OHM
2.44 cubic feet
2.1 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
9298384
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 03, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of oral history interview audio masters.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5796: NAA Additional Records 5775: NAA Records 6004: NAA Additional Records 6004 AV: NAA Audio-Visual Material 6004 OHT: NAA History Committee Oral History Interview Transcripts 6205: NAA Committee Files 5246: NAA Records 6204: NAA Restricted Committee Files 6136: Dennis Nolan Collection of National Academy of Arbitrators History Files
Industrial relations; Arbitration, Industrial; Collective labor agreements; Mediation and conciliation, Industrial; Aaron, Benjamin; Abernethy, Byron R.; Alexander, Gabriel; Anderson, Arvid; Bairstow, Frances; Block, Howard; Block, Richard; Dash, G. Allen; Dunsford, John E.; Dybeck, Alfred C.; Elson, Alex; Fallon, William J.; Feller, David; Fleming, Robben; Garrett, Sylvester; Gershenfeld, Gladys; Gershenfeld, Walter; Gill, Lewis; Gruenberg, Gladys W.; Harkless, James; Jones, Dallas; Jones, Edgar A.; Kagel, John; Kagel, Sam; Kahn, Mark L.; Kelliher, Peter M.; Killingsworth, Charles C.; Larkin, John Day; Luskin, Bert L.; McDermott, Clare B.; McKelvey, Jean T.(Jean Trepp), 1908-1998.; Mittenthal, Richard; Murphy, William; Nicolau, George; Platt, Harry H.; Robbins, Eva; Roberts, Thomas T.; Rock, Eli; Rubin, Milton; Seward, Ralph T. (Ralph Theodore), 1907-; Sherman, James; Sherman, Marilyn; Simkin, William E.; Sinicropi, Anthony; Smith, Russel A.; St. Antoine, Theodore J., 1929-; Stark, Arthur; Valtin, Rolf; Zack, Arnold; National Academy of Arbitrators; National Academy of Arbitrators. History Committee.
9298384
- Russell Smith (11/30/1990) (Box 1)
- Al Dybeck Interview, 11/2/1991 (Box 2)
- NAA - Fleming - Wirtz -- 5/27/1992 (Box 3)
- Interviewee - Gladys Gruenberg / Interviewer- Joyce Najita (10/13/2006) (Box 4)
- R. Black Interview - 5/29/1996 (tape #3) (Box 5)
- Feller (Box 6)
- Feller #2 (Box 7)
- Ralph T. Seward; William E. Simkin (Box 8)
- Ralph T. Seward -- 1947-1949 (Box 9)
- Tony Sinicropi and Arnie Zack -- 6/4/1993 (Box 10)
- Arnie Zack - 6/4/1993 (Box 11)
- Arnie Zack - 6/4/1993 (Box 12)
- Harkless Interview, 1995 (Box 13)
- James Harkless Interview by Clara H. Friedman - 11/10/1995 (Box 14)
- Harkless Interview, 1995 (Box 15)
- Harkless Interview - 11/10/1995 (Box 16)
- Tom Roberts - 10/2/1990 (Box 17)
- Lewis Gill - 8/29/1990 (Box 18)
- R. Block Interview - 5/28/1996 (tape #1) (Box 19)